http://www.enjoylifefoods.com/pages/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Search
what are you looking for?
FREE ground ship on orders $49+
Shop Shop AllVariety PacksBest SellersSeasonalChocolateCookiesSnack BarsSnacksVeganFodmap FriendlySubscribeLearn Free from foodsFodmap FriendlyIngredientsFAQsAllergy Friendly PromiseGluten Intolerance & Celiac DiseaseFood AllergiesNon-GMOKosher & HalalRecipes View All RecipesSeasonalDessertsEntreesSnacksBreakfastConnect Contact UsOur storyOur BlogMedia centerOur BakeryEventsFind A Store
Log in
Locate a store
0
items
Shipping & taxes calculated at checkout
Your cart is currently empty.
0
items
$0.00
Continue Shopping
Continue Shopping
0
items
Shipping & taxes calculated at checkout
Your cart is currently empty.
0
items
$0.00
Continue Shopping
Continue Shopping
Your cart is currently empty.
Shipping & taxes calculated at checkout
This order is a gift
How thoughtful of you! Now send a short message that will ship with your gift. The recipient will know it's from you, but they won't see any pricing.
Continue Shopping
[[ formatted_image ]]
[[ product_title ]]
##OPTIONS##
[[ variant_title ]]
##OPTIONS##
[[ formatted_price ]]
Quantity
##QUANTITIES##
[[ quantity_index ]]
##QUANTITIES##
Delivery
Remove
##DISCOUNT_DESCRIPTION##
[[ discount_description ]]
##DISCOUNT_DESCRIPTION##
Anchor example
This modal can be opened by clicking the anchor icon in the pre-header.
Because the link uses an href anchor (instead of data-open-modal) you'll see #example_modal in your address bar.
If you want to see the hidden modal, manually change the url in your address bar to #hidden_modal.
data-open-modal example
This modal can be opened by clicking the window icon in the pre-header.
Because the link uses data-open-modal (instead of an href anchor) nothing appears in the address bar. You also can't use the back/forward buttons to close or reopen the modal. However, if you know the ID of the modal, you can still manually type the anchor link in your address bar and it will open (handy for client previews).
To simulate an extremely long modal and show how modals scroll, here's a ton of lorem ipsum:
Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit. Rerum fugit, aperiam qui ducimus incidunt quis ad saepe at! Quis pariatur id nemo iusto. Delectus doloremque, voluptates dicta ab ullam quibusdam!
Illo debitis nihil, labore impedit voluptates soluta asperiores dignissimos dolorem cupiditate optio possimus, accusamus sit libero magni saepe quae explicabo obcaecati laboriosam! Veniam nobis incidunt nam cum a quasi voluptas commodi voluptates rerum dolore nulla nihil numquam perspiciatis at blanditiis odio similique, consequuntur et.
Consequuntur doloremque distinctio quis aperiam quidem labore nisi aspernatur necessitatibus, perspiciatis quas nulla exercitationem voluptate cupiditate natus? Aperiam cum unde ut doloribus! Aliquid omnis aperiam, magni iure exercitationem numquam quas blanditiis repellendus. Debitis error reprehenderit, laboriosam praesentium neque porro placeat dignissimos dicta natus adipisci!
Ipsam blanditiis neque rerum, saepe nam assumenda odio sed nostrum dolorum sint exercitationem repellat necessitatibus provident aliquam quod tenetur voluptatibus sapiente perspiciatis! Maxime, consectetur quae. Repellendus vitae minima distinctio, esse, iste ut quibusdam nemo doloremque iure eum ex deserunt illum at voluptatum quisquam aperiam?
Dolorem facilis aspernatur explicabo deserunt a provident iste consequuntur, earum, odit iusto cupiditate odio. Molestias aspernatur quo reprehenderit voluptatem accusamus tenetur natus. Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipisicing elit. Illo magnam, totam omnis pariatur voluptatum ullam in, cumque error unde cupiditate molestias nihil accusantium dolorum accusamus quo odit. Nulla, nostrum ex.
Eum vel natus iusto provident atque quis officia, adipisci quibusdam. Esse, officia doloribus corporis eius optio accusamus natus error iure ducimus sed? Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet consectetur adipisicing elit. Eius libero sequi quis sint reprehenderit accusantium laudantium nam eos delectus blanditiis, recusandae consectetur qui sed totam beatae et ratione dolorum quae?
Hidden modal
This modal has no link to it.
The only way you can find or open it is by manually entering #hidden_modal in the address bar.
Welcome!
It looks like you're located in:
Would you like to visit
instead?
Yes, take me there!
No, I'll stay here
Shop These Ingredients
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Scope
This privacy statement applies to www.enjoylifefoods.com and Enjoy Life Foods websites, services, applications and products that collect data and display these terms (collectively, our “sites”). It does not apply to services and products that do not display or link to this statement or that have their own privacy statements.
Information We Collect
Enjoy Life Foods collects many types of information in order to operate effectively and provide you the best products, services and experiences we can. This information includes:
Information you provide (for example, when you register with our sites, sign up for our newsletters or email lists, participate in surveys and purchase our products or services);
Information collected automatically (for example, we may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies that collect non-personal information about your use of our sites, interactions with our emails, and information about your computer and web browser);
Information collected from other sources (for example, we may collect information from commercially available sources such as data aggregators and public databases);
We may also combine this information to help us tailor our communications and advertisements to you, develop exceptional products and services, and improve our sites. Information Collected Automatically by Our Partners;
We also use third party ad networks and similar providers to serve advertisements on our sites. These providers may use cookies and similar technologies to collect non-personal information such as your IP address. They may also use anonymous data received from third parties to assist them in delivering more meaningful advertisements to you; and
Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit and/or debit card numbers), email address, phone number, IP address, and location information.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.”  Additionally, users provide some or all of this information in order to create an account, access various content or features in our webpage, submit content, change your communication preferences or profile, or directly contact us with questions or feedback.
Your Ability To Control Cookies And Similar Technologies
Cookies, web beacons, Flash cookies and similar technologies serve many important functions that help us serve you better. However, you have a variety of tools to control cookies and similar technologies, including:
Web browser controls to block and delete cookies, or adjust your tracking preferences;
Visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out page here to opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies; and
Information on how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies here.
How We Use Your Personal Information
Enjoy Life Foods uses the information we collect for many important purposes, including to:
Provide the products and services you request;
Communicate with you regarding our products and services, as well as those of our partners and affiliates;
To address problems and review the usage and operations of our sites or business and improve our content, products, and services;
Share or post reviews of our products and services; and
Display more meaningful and relevant advertisements.
How We Share Your Personal Information
Enjoy Life Foods does not sell or disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties without your consent, except where:
We engage third-party service providers to assist us with the activities identified in this privacy statement. In these situations, we only allow these providers to use your personal information as necessary to perform activities on our behalf or to comply with a legal requirement;
We conduct joint promotions with other companies and sharing your personal information is necessary to conduct the promotion. We will not share your personal information with our promotional partners for any other reason;
It is necessary to prevent crime or injury, or as otherwise required by law;
Another company acquires us or any of our assets; and
We may share personally identifiable information among Enjoy Life Foods brands, affiliates and subsidiaries. In the course of doing business, we employ other companies and individuals to perform a variety of functions on our behalf. For example, we hire agencies to help administer consumer promotions, to analyze data, to fulfill orders you place, and to provide customer service. These service providers may have access to personally identifiable information about our website visitors if it is needed to perform their functions for Enjoy Life Foods, but they are not authorized by Enjoy Life Foods to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on Enjoy Life Foods’ behalf or to comply with legal requirements, and they are required to maintain the information in confidence.
How We Protect Your Personal Information
Enjoy Life Foods maintains administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect your personal information against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration, or destruction of the personally identifiable information we collect on our sites.
Choice And Control Over Your Personal Information
To change how Enjoy Life Foods contacts you, to correct or change your information or to cancel your registration with us, you can either update your information in the Your Profile section of our sites or email our Online Team using the form found at the following page.
Your California Privacy Rights
For California Residents Only. Enjoy Life Foods may share your personal information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the Enjoy Life Foods name, for their own direct marketing purposes. If you would like to learn more about the types of personal information we share and who we share it with, please send us a letter with the heading “California Privacy Rights” at: Enjoy Life Foods • 8770 W Bryn Mawr Ave Ste 1100 • Chicago IL 60631 • Attention: Legal Department.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
Enjoy Life Foods’ sites are intended for general audiences and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our sites.
We might permit a child to send us an e-mail. We will respond to or deliver these e-mails, but we do not store the names, e-mail addresses, or the e-mails themselves in our operational database. We do not maintain this information, nor do we share it with third parties (other than support service companies as described above).
Under federal law, websites directed to children under 13 are prohibited from conditioning a child's participation in an activity on the child's disclosing more personal information than is reasonably necessary to engage in the activity. We comply fully with this requirement.
Upon proper identification, any parent can review any personal information we have collected from their child, if we are still maintaining the information in our operational database. They may also request that the information be deleted from our database, and refuse to permit further collection or use of their child's information. If you are a parent and wish to exercise these rights, please contact us.
Other Information
Links To Other Sites
Enjoy Life Foods tries to make sure that any links on our sites send you to a helpful and reliable place on the Internet, but we are not responsible for the content of these other sites or their privacy practices.  Please check the privacy statement of the specific site you're visiting to understand the privacy practices associated with that site.
Public Forums And Reviews
You may use our sites to post reviews of our products and services, but once you do, it becomes public information and we may continue to display your content even if you terminate your account.
Updates To Our Privacy Statement
Check this privacy statement from time to time, as we may change or update portions of this statement at any time and without prior notice to you.  We will indicate the privacy policy’s effective date on the first page of the privacy policy.
How To Contact Us
Enjoy Life Foods • 8770 W Bryn Mawr Ave Ste 1100 • Chicago, IL 60631
Join Our CommunityGet the Enjoy Life email newsletter and become a part of our community! Stay informed with new product launches, store announcements, tasty recipes and more.
